[
    {"question": "in one ear, out the other", "answer": "何も聞いていない、聞き流す"},
    {"question": "drop the ball", "answer": "しくじる、ミスる"},
    {"question": "crunch time", "answer": "大事な時期、正念場"},
    {"question": "cut it out", "answer": "やめて"},
    {"question": "bittersweet", "answer": "甘く切ない、嬉し悲しい"},
    {"question": "on th ball", "answer": "頭が冴えた；（状況などを）把握した"},
    {"question": "put on a brave face", "answer": "平気そうな顔をする"},
    {"question": "make a fuss", "answer": "騒ぐ"},
    {"question": "off the top of one's head", "answer": "思いつくだけでも、確か"},
    {"question": "newbie", "answer": "初心者、新人"},
    {"question": "dig oneself into a hole", "answer": "墓穴を掘る"},
    {"question": "a piece of cake", "answer": "余裕、楽勝なこと"},
    {"question": "have a high standards", "answer": "基準が高い、理想が高い"},
    {"question": "on the house", "answer": "無料の"},
    {"question": "out of left field", "answer": "突然"},
    {"question": "jog sb's memory", "answer": "〜の記憶を思い出させる"},
    {"question": "get away with sth", "answer": "〜しても許される、切り抜ける"},
    {"question": "no-brainer", "answer": "考えるまでもないこと"},
    {"question": "on the same wavelength", "answer": "波長が合う"},
    {"question": "away", "answer": "不在の"},

    {"question": "kick-start with sth", "answer": "～に弾みをつける、始動させる"},
    {"question": "the last straw", "answer": "我慢できなくなる原因"},
    {"question": "almost there", "answer": "もうちょっと（で終わる）"},
    {"question": "shoot oneself in the foot", "answer": "墓穴を掘る"},
    {"question": "keep track of sth/sb", "answer": "～の状況を把握する、動きを追う"},
    {"question": "keep sb posted", "answer": "～に何かあったら教える"},
    {"question": "get straight to the point", "answer": "すぐ本題に入る"},
    {"question": "I don't know about that", "answer": "それはどうかな"},
    {"question": "bounce off the walls", "answer": "元気いっぱいである"},
    {"question": "gather one's thoughts", "answer": "考えをまとめる"},
    {"question": "ground rules", "answer": "基本的なルール"},
    {"question": "for real", "answer": "マジな；本当に"},
    {"question": "long story short", "answer": "早い話、簡単に言うと"},
    {"question": "one-size-fits-all", "answer": "誰にでも合う"},
    {"question": "on the top of sth", "answer": "～を把握した"},
    {"question": "sb's thing", "answer": "～が好きなこと；いつものこと"},
    {"question": "think on sth", "answer": "～をよく考える、検討する"},
    {"question": "switched on", "answer": "賢い、てきばきした"},
    {"question": "ease into sth", "answer": "～をゆっくり始める、慣れる"},
    {"question": "true that", "answer": "その通りだ、それな"},

    {"question": "head", "answer": "行く、向かう"},
    {"question": "slip sb's mind", "answer": "～を忘れる"},
    {"question": "burn one's bridges", "answer": "後戻りできなくなる、関係を断つ"},
    {"question": "settle down", "answer": "（気持ちが）落ち着く"},
    {"question": "sure thing", "answer": "了解、もちろん"},
    {"question": "one-sided", "answer": "一方的な"},
    {"question": "get sth off one's chest", "answer": "～を打ち明ける"},
    {"question": "free sth up", "answer": "～の余裕をつくる"},
    {"question": "catch sb off guard", "answer": "～を驚かせる、不意をつく"},
    {"question": "buy sth", "answer": "～を信じる"},
    {"question": "cheap shot", "answer": "卑怯なやり方"},
    {"question": "out of nowhere", "answer": "いつの間に、突然"},
    {"question": "go on (and on) about sth", "answer": "～についてずっと話す、語る"},
    {"question": "put one's heads together", "answer": "協力する"},
    {"question": "the reality is (that)", "answer": "実際は"},
    {"question": "back and forth", "answer": "あれこれ議論"},
    {"question": "lose track of time", "answer": "時間が経つのを忘れる"},
    {"question": "across the board", "answer": "全面的に"},
    {"question": "big picture", "answer": "全体像"},
    {"question": "fly under the radar", "answer": "目立たないようにする"},

    {"question": "for all intents and purposes", "answer": "どう見ても、事実上"},
    {"question": "upbeat", "answer": "ポジティブな、明るい"},
    {"question": "change it up", "answer": "環境を変える"},
    {"question": "play one's cards right", "answer": "うまくやる、うまく立ち回る"},
    {"question": "cream of the crop", "answer": "一番のもの、最も優秀な人"},
    {"question": "in good shape", "answer": "状態が良い；体調が言い"},
    {"question": "wouldn't hurt to do", "answer": "（とりあえす）～してもいい"},
    {"question": "down the road", "answer": "将来的には、ゆくゆくは"},
    {"question": "thick-skinned", "answer": "神経が図太い、打たれ強い"},
    {"question": "life of the party", "answer": "盛り上げ役、ムードメーカー"},
    {"question": "quality over quantity", "answer": "量より質"},
    {"question": "make a call", "answer": "決める"},
    {"question": "for argument's sake", "answer": "仮に"},
    {"question": "plan of attack", "answer": "具体的なプラン"},
    {"question": "get off to a rough start", "answer": "滑り出しが良くない"},
    {"question": "open (up) a can of worms", "answer": "（物事を）ややこしくする"},
    {"question": "pick up the pace", "answer": "ペースを上げる"},
    {"question": "chip away at sth", "answer": "～にコツコツ取り組む"},
    {"question": "pick sth up", "answer": "（悪いことや趣味を）始める"},
    {"question": "get under sb's skin", "answer": "イライラさせる"},

    {"question": "on board with sth", "answer": "〜に賛成した"},
    {"question": "keep sb in the loop", "answer": "〜に何かあったら教える"},
    {"question": "wishful thinking", "answer": "だといいな、希望的観測"},
    {"question": "if it were up to me", "answer": "もし自分が決めていいなら"},
    {"question": "keep it between us", "answer": "誰にも言わない、秘密にする"},
    {"question": "make sb's day", "answer": "〜の最高の一日になる"},
    {"question": "book-smart", "answer": "頭が良い（けど残念な）"},
    {"question": "street-smart", "answer": "世渡り上手な"},
    {"question": "backstabber", "answer": "裏切り者"},
    {"question": "I'm game", "answer": "もちろん、いいよ"},
    {"question": "get one's act together", "answer": "しっかりする、ちゃんとする"},
    {"question": "at the end of the day", "answer": "結局は"},
    {"question": "drive a hard bargain", "answer": "強気の交渉をする"},
    {"question": "might as well (do)", "answer": "〜しておく、してもいい"},
    {"question": "high-level", "answer": "大まかな、ざっくりした"},
    {"question": "in the mix", "answer": "候補に入った"},
    {"question": "stack up", "answer": "つじつまがあう"},
    {"question": "one way or another", "answer": "なんとかして、なんとしてでも"},
    {"question": "not the end of the world", "answer": "大したことではない"},
    {"question": "hit it off", "answer": "意気投合する、仲良くなる"}
]